footytips.com.au 2014-01-25

# Footy Tipping Marketing Solutions - Powered by footytips.com.au

**ESPN Australia takes privacy seriously.**

This Privacy Policy applies to the services offered on the www.footytips.com.au web sites offered by ESPN Australia Pty Ltd (ABN 40 091 402 327) ("ESPN Australia"). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using the ESPN Australia web site or any site owned by ESPN Australia. Usage of the ESPN Australia web site is conditional upon you agreeing to be bound by this privacy policy. 

In summary, while you should read each provision in this Privacy Policy, you must note that by using the ESPN Australia website: 

  * You agree that if you submit your personal information to us, we may create a database record about you; 
  * You agree for us to use cookies on your browser (unless you remove them - please see below for explanation); 

**1\. Your personal information is important to us**  
ESPN Australia is committed to safeguarding your personal privacy. We recognise that you have a right to control how your personal information is collected and used. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that seriously. 

Unless you directly give us consent to do otherwise, ESPN Australia will only collect and use your personal information as set out below. 

**2\. Our services**  
ESPN Australia offers a variety of services on our web site related to our products, which might be of interest to you. These services may have specific conditions, which are explained at the time when you purchase those services, in addition to this general Privacy Policy. 

**3\. Collecting information about you**  
ESPN Australia will not collect or monitor any personal information about you without your consent. The only personal information we collect is what you tell us about yourself. 

When you apply for a product from us (online or in a face to face with one of our representatives), we may ask for your personal information (such as name and address) in order to service your application. You do not have to provide us with this information if that is your preference. However, failure to do so may result in ESPN Australia being unable to sell you products and/or provide certain services including after services. 

**4\. Our use of cookies & clear GIFs**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. ESPN Australia uses cookies to make your use of our website and services as convenient as possible. Cookies do not themselves personally identify users, although they do identify a user's browser. Cookies allow us to remember the information you have entered as you move through our site, and let us know how many people are using the different parts of the site. If you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to refuse cookies. However, this may mean you will not be able to take full advantage of ESPN Australia's web site. 

ESPN Australia may also use web tools known as clear GIFs on our site, email communications and on the web sites of our affiliates, partners or clients. Clear GIFs do not store or contain any personally identifiable information but they allow us to track the effectiveness of promotions or campaign activity. 

ESPN Australia can track user-activity on our partners', advertisers' clients' or affiliates' sites. This system uses a combination of a cookie and a clear GIF to enable us to identify actions that you have taken in response to a promotion or an email. By disabling support for cookies in your browser, we will be unable to recognise your actions and this may affect your entitlements. This system does not allow any third-party to access any of your personally identifiable information. 

**5\. Using and disclosing your personal information**  
We intend to use your information for the following purposes only: 

  * To fulfil our obligation under any contract and/or any other contract between you and ESPN Australia.
  * To provide you with information about our products, service and/or special offers.
  * To ask you for your opinion or comments about our products and/or services.
  * To track general traffic patterns showing the usage of our web site.

Please also note that in order to operate the web site or deliver a service we may sometimes share your personal information with a financial institution, a non-ESPN Australia company. 

As ESPN Australia recognise the trust you place in us when you give us personal information, we will not use or disclose any information about you for other purposes without your consent, except for in exceptional cases such as if disclosure is required by laws or is necessary to protect the rights or property of ESPN Australia, or any member of the public, or to lessen a serious threat to a person's health or safety. 

**6\. When we will contact you**   
We may contact you at the email or other address which you provide to us in order to: 

  * Provide you with information which may be of interest about updates, new ESPN Australia products and other matters which may interest you.
  * Send you a newsletter.
  * Provide information about our sponsors.

If you are receiving communications from ESPN Australia and do not wish to receive this information any longer, you may remove your name from our list by emailing us at the email address contained in the Contact form. 

**7\. Storage and security of your personal information**  
ESPN Australia will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information, which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. Your information is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. Our employees and data processors are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by ESPN Australia. However, as we cannot guarantee the security of communications over the Internet, we cannot give an absolute assurance that your information will be secure at all times. ESPN Australia will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information. 

**8\. ESPN Australia and links to other web sites**  
ESPN Australia provides links to web sites outside of the ESPN Australia site. These linked sites are not under the control of ESPN Australia, and we are not responsible for the conduct of companies linked to our web site. Before disclosing your personal information on any other web site, we advise you to examine the Terms and Conditions of those web sites. 

**9\. Accessing personal information held**  
If at any time you want to know what information we hold about you, you are welcome to request your personal information by emailing us at the contact address located on the Contact form on this site. If you want to change and correct personal information that is inaccurate or out of date, please email us at the before mentioned email address. To have personal information deleted, please let us know in the same manner, and we will take reasonable steps to delete your personal information unless we need to keep it for legal reasons. 

**10\. What to do if you have a problem or question**  
If ESPN Australia becomes aware of any ongoing concerns or problems with areas on our website, we will take these issues seriously and work to address these concerns. If you have any further queries relating to our Privacy Policy, or you have a problem or complaint, please contact us by clicking on the Contact page and submitting an enquiry via the email address located on this page. 

**11\. Future changes**  
Our commitment to be a leading provider of online services means that our business will continue to evolve as we introduce new services and features to our web site. Because of this, from time to time, our policies will be reviewed and may be revised. ESPN Australia reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time and notify you by posting an updated version of the policy on its web site. The amended Privacy Policy will apply between us whether or not we have given you specific notice of any change. 

For more information regarding this policy, please contact us at: 

**Privacy Officer**  
C/- ESPN Australia  
Level 3, 68 York St  
Sydney NSW 2000, Australia  
Phone: (03) 9832 6000  
Email:

Last updated: 5th June 2013
